spiritvoyage.com 2019-03-20

# Spirit Voyage : Privacy Policy

### SPIRIT VOYAGE PRIVACY POLICY 

By visiting SpiritVoyage.com , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Your Spirit Voyage Account: SpiritVoyage.com collect s personal information that you provide when using our website. This information includes your first and last name, email address and a password when you create your account. You can browse our site without creating an account and can check out anonymously, but you will need to create an account to take advantage of certain features, such as our "Wish List," "Address Book" and other SpiritVoyage.com services. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. 

Purchasing: When you purchase online at SpiritVoyage.com, we save your name and payment information, such as credit card information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address and phone number of the intended recipient. 

Cookies: We use cookies which collects information about where you visit on our website. The purpose of cookies are to identify you when you visit our website so that we can personalize your online shopping experience. You can choose to browse on SpiritVoyage.com without cookies; however, without cookies you will not be able to take advantage of certain features of our website. Each browser is different, so check your browser’s Help menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

Sharing Information : We never sell information to third parties. We do not share your information with external businesses or entities except when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of SpiritVoyage.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Protecting Your Information: The security of your personal information is very important to us. To protect your online transactions, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). Using SSL, your personal information will be autom ca atically encrypted before it is sent over the Internet. SpiritVoyage.com is Hacker Safe certifi ed on a daily basis. Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you signed up for an account at SpiritVoyage.com (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to My Spirit Voyage.
